[
    {
        "question": "The loss of his job ............ a negative impact on him.",
        "choices": [
            "had",
            "took",
            "provide",
            "did"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "had"
    },
    {
        "question": "We need to ............ more research into coronavirus.",
        "choices": [
            "go",
            "do",
            "get",
            "leave"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "Young men join the army after ............ school or university.",
        "choices": [
            "going",
            "doing",
            "getting",
            "leaving"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "getting"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I was young, I ............ missing when I was shopping with my mum.",
        "choices": [
            "went",
            "did",
            "got",
            "left"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "To ............ wild animals is a crime.",
        "choices": [
            "kill",
            "kills",
            "killing",
            "killings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "kill"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. wild animals is a crime.",
        "choices": [
            "Kill",
            "Kills",
            "Killing",
            "Killings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Killing"
    },
    {
        "question": "The new wildlife law has helped reduce ............ among rare animals.",
        "choices": [
            "kill",
            "kills",
            "killing",
            "killings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "killings"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Lion Guardians is an organization based ............ Kenya.",
        "choices": [
            "on",
            "in",
            "at",
            "to"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "question": "This film is based ............ a true story.",
        "choices": [
            "in",
            "on",
            "of",
            "with"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "question": "He succeeded in his life thanks ............ hard work.",
        "choices": [
            "for",
            "to",
            "from",
            "about"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "to"
    },
    {
        "question": "People don't drink as ............ as camels do.",
        "choices": [
            "long",
            "well",
            "much",
            "soon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "much"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doing sport is part of my ............ activities.",
        "choices": [
            "angel",
            "angle",
            "everyday",
            "every day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "every day"
    },
    {
        "question": "I do sport ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "angel",
            "angle",
            "everyday",
            "every day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "every day"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finally, I heard ............ my brother in the USA. He sent me an email.",
        "choices": [
            "from",
            "of",
            "about",
            "b & c"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "b & c"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have just heard ............ your health problems.",
        "choices": [
            "from",
            "of",
            "about",
            "b & c"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "b & c"
    }
]